<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="lesson_general_vowels">To start off our vowel lessons, we need to understand the
        general mechanics of vowels. First, we need to explain one of the most important rules of
        vowels; <font color="#ffbc3a">Vowels cannot be a standalone letter in the Korean language</font>.

        \n\n<font color="#ffbc3a">Vowels cannot be used as a starting letter for any syllable
            block</font>. Hence, <font color="#ffbc3a">they need a starting consonant that occupies
            the starting field of any syllable block that they will be used in</font>.

        \n\nBut <font color="#ffbc3a">how are we going to use vowels without having their sound
            modified by a consonant?</font> Well, as mentioned in the previous lessons,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㅇ</font> is a consonant that is
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Silent</font> when used
        <font color="#ffbc3a">as a starting consonant</font>. Hence, you can always
        <font color="#ffbc3a">use it as a placeholder</font> so you can use a vowel as a standalone
        sound.

        \n\nHere are some examples:
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_general_vowels_2">By writing vowels in this way, we can retain the vowel\'s
        sound without being modified by the starting consonants sound!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_vertical_vowels">Vertical vowels are pretty straight-forward;
        <font color="#ffbc3a">they are vowels that stand vertically in a syllable block and every
            rule that a vowel has is also applied to them</font>.
        If you haven\'t checked the rules of a vowel, we recommend checking the prerequisite lesson
        above!

        \n\nNow that we got that out of the way, it\'s time to take a look at all the Korean vowels!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_vertical_vowel_cheatsheet">Here we can see the vertical vowel cheatsheet.
        In this figure, <font color="#ffbc3a">each Korean letter is accompanied by a Roman letter</font>.
        In Romanized hangul, <font color="#ffbc3a">these letters are their Roman letter equivalent</font>.
        However, while they are in <font color="#ffbc3a">similar sound, they are not entirely the same</font>.

        \n\nOther than that, we could see some
        <font color="#ffbc3a">letter combinations in the figure above</font>. For example, the
        letter ㅑ is a a combination of the letter Y and the letter A which makes the
        sound of \"Ya\". <font color="#ffbc3a">This is a common sight in the Korean language</font>
        and despite containing the consonant letter Y in the Roman writing system, the vowel ㅑ is
        considered as a whole vowel in the Korean writing system.

        \n\nNow that we\'ve seen the Korean vertical vowels\' Romanized equivalents, let\'s take a look
        at how they would look like in actual syllable blocks.

        \n\nHere are some examples:
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_vertical_vowel_cheatsheet_2">Here we can see different vertical vowels used
        in a syllable block. As you can see, they always stand vertically at the right side of the
        consonant as the name implies.

        \n\nLet\'s break-down the syllable blocks. For example, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">안</font>.
        As mentioned in the previous lessons, the letter ㅇ when placed as a beginning consonant is silent.
        Therefore, <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㅇ should be read as a silent sound</font>.
        Next, <font color="#ffbc3a">beside it is the ㅏ vertical vowel</font>. According to the
        cheat sheet above, <font color="#ffbc3a">the ㅏ\'s sound is similar to the letter A</font>.
        Which means that if we combine the letter ㅇ and ㅏ together, <font color="#ffbc3a">it should
            result into 아, which is read as \"Ah\" or \"A\"</font>. Easy, right? Now we for the last
        part, <font color="#ffbc3a">we have the consonant letter ㄴ on the bottom part of the
            syllable block</font>. This is a consonant hence it is currently not part of the lesson.
        However, in the Romanized version, the letter ㄴ\'s equivalent is the letter N. Hence, adding
        it to the mix, the letter ㅇ and ㅏ combined into 아 should sound as \"Ah\" while adding the
        letter ㄴ at the bottom of it to complete the syllable block 안 would create the sound
        \"An\" or \"Ahn\"!

        \n\nTo familiarize yourself with these vertical vowels, we recommend trying to write down
        your own syllable blocks using the cumulative knowledge you\'ve gained from all of the
        previous lessons. Try it out!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_horizontal_vowels">Similar to Vertical Vowels, Horizontal vowels are as
        the name implies:
        <font color="#ffbc3a">they are vowels that are placed horizontally on a syllable block</font>.
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Most of the time, horizontal vowels are always underneath the
            starting consonant of a syllable block</font>. This means that they are often occupying
        the 2nd field of the syllable block!

        \n\nWith that said, that means horizontal vowels will also require a starting consonant as
        mentioned in the pre-requisite lesson. If you haven\'t checked it yet, please read the lesson
        before proceeding!

        \n\nNow, let\'s take a look at the Korean horizontal vowels!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_horizontal_vowel_cheatsheet">The figure above is the Horizontal Vowel cheatsheet.
        As you can see, it is very much similar to the Vertical Vowels from the previous lesson. However,
        this time, <font color="#ffbc3a">the vertical vowels are placed horizontally underneath
        the starting consonant</font>.

        \n\nSimilar to the previous lesson, the same thing goes to this horizontal vowel cheatsheet.
        Each horizontal vowel is accompanied by a Roman letter that is similar in sound.
        Use these as your guide for learning the sounds of the horizontal vowels.

        \n\nNow that we\'ve seen the horizontal vowels, let\'s see how they would look in syllable blocks!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_horizontal_vowel_cheatsheet_2">If we look at these examples, we could see that
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the horizontal vowel is always underneath the ㅇ consonant or starting consonant</font>.

        \n\nLet\'s break down a syllable block. For example, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">용</font>.
        As mentioned in previous lessons, <font color="#ffbc3a">the consonant ㅇ when used as a
            beginning consonant, it should be silent</font>. Next, <font color="#ffbc3a">we have the
            ㅛ vowel underneath it</font>. According to the cheat sheet, <font color="#ffbc3a">the ㅛ\'s
            sound should be similar to the Roman letters Y and O combined into \"Yo\"</font>.
        Which means, <font color="#ffbc3a">요 together should be \"YO\"</font>.
        However, <font color="#ffbc3a">there is still another ㅇ consonant at the ending consonant
            position</font>. As mentioned in the previous lessons, when the letter ㅇ is used as an
        ending consonant, <font color="#ffbc3a">it should be read as the \"NG\" sound</font>.
        Therefore, the syllable block
        <font color="#ffbc3a">용 altogether should be read as \"Yong\"</font>.

        \n\nTry practicing by making your own syllable blocks from what you\'ve learned!
    </string>

</resources>