<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="lesson_reading_order"><font color="#ffbc3a">The Korean reading order is very similar
        to the syllable block Stroke Order</font>.

        \n\nLet\'s refresh our memory. What is the Stroke Order? Each syllable block has specific
        fields and numbers that indicate the arrangement of how you will write the syllable block.
        The lower the number, often times found at the top-left of the syllable block, the first comes
        in terms of reading and writing it. The higher the number, often found at the bottom-right of
        the syllable block, the later they are added or read in the syllable block.

        \n\nThese syllable block rules also applies to the Korean Reading Order in the same manner
        and order.

        \n\nNow that we remember the previous lessons, let\'s try out what we know!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_reading_order_2">In the first syllable block we have
        <font color="#ffbc3a">한</font>, a 3-letter syllable block with <font color="#ffbc3a">ㅎ as
            the starting consonant</font>. According to the reading order, we should
        <font color="#ffbc3a">start from ㅎ then ㅏ and the last should be ㄴ</font>. If we refer to
        the previous lessons from the writing topic, we should already know what these letters
        sound like. So ㅎ should be H, ㅏ should be A, and ㄴ should be N. Therefore, the 1st
        syllable block is read as <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Han\"</font>.

        \n\nUp next, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">글</font>, another 3-letter syllable block with
        <font color="#ffbc3a">ㄱ as the starting consonant, ㅡ as its horizontal vowel, and ㄹ as
            its ending consonant</font>. Based off the reading order, we should be starting from the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">top-left to the bottom-right</font>. Therefore, ㄱ should be G, ㅡ should
        be \"eu\" and ㄹ should be L. <font color="#ffbc3a">글 should be read as \"Geul\"</font>.
        However, the <font color="#ffbc3a">Batchim rule</font> applies to this syllable block.
        Which means the ㄹ should be R instead of L. So <font color="#ffbc3a">when the Batchim rule
            is followed, this syllable block should be \"Geur\"</font>. For now, we\'ll go with the
        Batchim rule to make sure the words are read correctly and explain it afterwards.

        \n\nFor the third syllable block, we have 을. Again, top-left to the bottom-right. We should
        start from ㅇ which is the starting consonant, ㅡ as the horizontal vowel, and ㄹ as the ending
        consonant. <font color="#ffbc3a">The procedure is the same</font>; ㅇ is the starting consonant
        which is silent, ㅡ as \"eu\" and ㄹ is equivalent to L. Which means
        <font color="#ffbc3a">을 is read as \"Eul\"</font>.

        \n\nNow, with all the syllable blocks combined, the first set of words should be read as
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Han-geur-eul\"</font>.

        \n\nFor the second set of words, let\'s try breaking it down all together. Our first syllable
        is <font color="#ffbc3a">즐</font>. Following the same process, we should end up with
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Jeul\"</font>. Next, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">겨</font>, a
        horizontal 2-letter syllable block and <font color="#ffbc3a">요</font>, a vertical 2-letter
        syllable block. With the two read as <font color="#ffbc3a">겨 = \"Gyeo\"</font> and
        <font color="#ffbc3a">요 = \"Yo\"</font> respectively. When combined, these syllable blocks
        should be <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Jeul-Gyeo-Yo\"</font>.

        \n\nWhen both sets of words are combined,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Han-geur-eul Jeul-Gyeo-Yo (한글을 즐겨요)</font> means
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"I enjoy Hangul\"</font> or <font color="#ffbc3a">\"I enjoy Korean\"</font>.
    </string>

</resources>