<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="lesson_batchim">Batchim is one of the most complicated parts of the Korean reading
        and writing system. However, we can still discuss the most basic parts of Batchim to kickstart
        your Korean learning journey!

        \n\nBatchim is <font color="#ffbc3a">commonly found at the bottom or final consonant of a
        syllable block</font>. When it comes to Batchim, there are some <font color="#ffbc3a">Korean
        letters that may change their sound</font> depending if Bathchim applies to them or not.

        \n\nTo make things easier to understand here\'s an example situation:
        \n\nLet\'s use the word <font color="#ffbc3a">Batchim (받침)</font> for example. If
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Batchim is not applied</font>, the word
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"받침\"</font> itself should be read as
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Bad-Chim\"</font>. However,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">when rules of Batchim is applied</font>, it
        should be <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Batchim\"</font> wherein the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">letter ㄷ\'s sound</font> in the syllable 받 is
        <font color="#ffbc3a">replaced with T
            instead of the usual D sound</font>.

        \n\nHowever, this does not only apply to the letter ㄷ. There are more Korean letters sounds
        that can change when Batchim is applied.

        \n\nHere are some examples:
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_batchim_2">If you look at the figure above, we can see the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Korean letters on the left side</font> and their
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Latin or Roman letter counterpart on the right side</font> when
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Batchim
            is applied</font>.

        \n\nOne example is the letter <font color="#ffbc3a">ㅅ</font>.
        Normally, the Korean <font color="#ffbc3a">letter ㅅ\'s sound should be similar
            to the letter S</font>. However in Batchim, its sound
        <font color="#ffbc3a">completely changes and turns into the T sound</font>.

        \n\nNow, you might be wondering: When do you apply batchim? Well, in the next lesson, we\'re
        going to discuss when are you supposed to apply Batchim when reading and writing Korean words.
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_batchim_3">When a syllable block
        <font color="#ffbc3a">ends with a consonant</font>, for example
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"받\"</font>
        and the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">next syllable block has a starting consonant</font>, for example
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"받침\"</font> the <font color="#ffbc3a">1st syllable
            block\'s ending consonant</font> needs to
        <font color="#ffbc3a">apply the Batchim rule</font>. Therefore,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the last consonant on
            the 1st syllable block</font> (Letter ㄷ) should
        <font color="#ffbc3a">sound similar to the letter T instead of the usual
            D sound</font>.

    </string>

    <string name="lesson_batchim_4">
        However, <font color="#ffbc3a">this does not apply</font> if the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">next syllable block\'s starting consonant is the letter
            ㅇ or the letter ㅎ</font>. In that case,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the final consonant on the 1st syllable block should retain
            its original sound</font>.

        \n\nHere is an example:
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_batchim_5">In cases like these,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Batchim should not be applied</font> therefore the letter
        <font color="#ffbc3a">ㄱ</font> in syllable block
        <font color="#ffbc3a">먹 retains its original G sound</font> instead of being modified
        <font color="#ffbc3a">into the K sound
            through Batchim</font>.

        \n\nNow that we\'ve finished the basics of reading, let\'s apply your new skills in reading
        exercises!
    </string>

</resources>