<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="lesson_consonants">Consonants in the Korean writing system are pretty easy to understand.
        One of its main rules is that <font color="#ffbc3a">it cannot be placed in between vowels</font>
        and the only positions it <font color="#ffbc3a">can only be placed in is the starting field</font>
        in a syllable block which is the top-left most part,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">and ending field</font> which is the bottom-right part or simply the bottom.

        \n\nHere are some examples:
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_consonants_2">As we can see above, all the consonants are either placed in the
        top-left of the syllable block or the bottom-right or simply bottom of the syllable block regardless
        of the letters that is accompanying it.

        \n\n<font color="#ffbc3a">Consonants that are placed in the top-left are considered as \"Starting Consonants\"</font>
        and the consonants that are written last in the
        <font color="#ffbc3a">bottom-right of a syllable block are the \"Ending Consonants\"</font>.

        \n\nNow that we\'ve familiarized ourselves with the positions of consonants, let\'s move on towards
        the consonant letters!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_consonant_letters">As we can see above, these Korean consonants are accompanied
        by Roman letters. These letters are in a similar sound with the Korean letters but not
        entirely the same.

        \n\nCompared to vowels, there are a lot more consonants in the
        Korean writing system. <font color="#ffbc3a">Some of these seems like duplicated letters but
            they are considered as one consonant therefore any rules that applies to any
            normal consonant also applies to them</font>.

        \n\nIn order to familiarize ourselves with these Korean letters, let\'s try doing an exercise!
    </string>

    <string name="lesson_consonant_letters_2">Let\'s take a look at the syllable blocks above. As we can see,
        the first syllable is <font color="#ffbc3a">나</font>, which <font color="#ffbc3a">consists
            of the consonant ㄴ and the vowel ㅏ</font>. It is <font color="#ffbc3a">a 2-letter syllable block</font>.
        If we refer to the cheat sheet above, we can see that <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄴ\'s
            sound is similar to the letter N</font>.
        And on the previous lesson, we found out that <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㅏ\'s sound is
            similar to the letter A</font>. Therefore, <font color="#ffbc3a">the syllable block 나
            should be read as \"Na\"</font>. It\'s that easy!

        \n\nNow, let\'s continue to the second syllable. Here we have <font color="#ffbc3a">는</font>,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">a 3-letter syllable block</font>. Which consists of <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄴ as
            the starting consonant</font>, with <font color="#ffbc3a">ㅡ as the horizontal vowel</font>,
        and <font color="#ffbc3a">another ㄴ as the ending consonant</font>. If we refer to the cheat sheet above,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄴ is similar to the letter N\'s sound</font>.
        And <font color="#ffbc3a">if we refer to the previous lesson for vowels, we
            found out that the letter ㅡ\'s sound is similar to \"EU\"</font>. And
        <font color="#ffbc3a">for the last, it\'s another ㄴ which is still the N sound</font>.
        If we combine these together into a syllable block, <font color="#ffbc3a">the
            syllable 는 should be read as \"Neun\"</font>.

        \n\nFor the third syllable, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">놀</font>. This is a bit trickier
        to explain due to batchim, but for now, we\'ll skip that topic. As we can see,
        <font color="#ffbc3a">the 놀 syllable has 3 letters, it is a 3-letter syllable block</font>
        that consists of <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄴ that is similar to the sound of N</font>,
        and <font color="#ffbc3a">the ㅗ if we refer to the previous lesson, it says that it sounds
            similar to the letter O</font>, and <font color="#ffbc3a">ㄹ which sounds similar to the
            letter R if we refer to the cheat sheet above</font>. If combined, <font color="#ffbc3a">it should be read as
            \"Nor\"</font>. But <font color="#ffbc3a">due to batchim, it is correctly
            read as \"Nol\"</font>.

        \n\nFor the 4th syllable, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">랍</font>, a
        <font color="#ffbc3a">3-letter syllable block</font>. It consists of <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄹ,
            which has a similar sound to the letter R</font>, and <font color="#ffbc3a">the vowel ㅏ,
            which has a similar sound to the letter A</font>, and <font color="#ffbc3a">the last
            letter, the letter ㅂ, which has a sound of the letter B</font>. If we combine
        these together, <font color="#ffbc3a">it should be read as \"Rab\"</font>. But
        <font color="#ffbc3a">due to batchim, it is correctly read as \"Rap\"</font>.

        \n\nFor the 5th and last syllable, we have <font color="#ffbc3a">다</font>, which should be
        simple. If we refer to the cheat sheet above, <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㄷ sounds
            similar to the letter D</font>. And if we refer to the previous lessons
        about vowels, <font color="#ffbc3a">the letter ㅏ should sound similar to the letter A</font>.
        <font color="#ffbc3a">Therefore, the syllable 다 should be read as \"Da\"</font>.

        \n\n<font color="#ffbc3a">When all of these syllables are combined</font>, it brings out
        the phrase <font color="#ffbc3a">\"나는 놀랍다\"</font> or
        <font color="#ffbc3a">\"Naneun Norrabda\"</font>. However, <font color="#ffbc3a">when batchim
            is applied, it is \"Naneun Nolrapda\"</font> which means <font color="#ffbc3a">\"I am amazing\"</font>.

        \n\n<font color="#ffbc3a">Congratulations! You just made your first phrase! Keep practicing and you\'ll be
            making your own phrases in no time!</font>
    </string>

</resources>